{
    "id": "36aa55937be04a1aa0ffcbf3bd145e44",
    "title": "Though, However, But, Despite",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "82d3ee9682a64ccd92f57f3c78d3d35a",
            "title": "Though, However, Despite, But",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "………………………….. his best efforts, he could not pass the test.",
                    "description": "Despite is a preposition. It is used before a noun or noun phrase. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Despite",
                        "However",
                        "Though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is not very beautiful …………………………, you cannot help liking her.",
                    "description": "However is a transitional adverb. In meaning it is similar to but, but it is not a conjunction. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "however",
                        "though",
                        "but"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………….. she was there, she refused to talk to me.",
                    "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "However",
                        "But"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I went to his home …………………………. I could not meet him.",
                    "description": "Use a full stop or a semicolon before however. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "however",
                        "but",
                        "though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………………. she was the most deserving candidate, she didn’t get the job.",
                    "description": "Though is a conjunction it is followed by a clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "However",
                        "Despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………….. her strange accent, I could understand her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "Despite",
                        "However"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She works three jobs …………………………….., she does not earn enough to make a living.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "however",
                        "but",
                        "despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………………. she is younger than me, she is the wiser of us two.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "Despite",
                        "However"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………………. their best efforts, they could not save her.",
                    "description": "Despite and in spite of mean the same. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "In spite of",
                        "Despite",
                        "Either could be used here."
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………………. hard you try, you will not be able to win.",
                    "description": "However hard means not matter how hard. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "However",
                        "Despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………………. they played to the best of their abilities, they could not win the match.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "Despite",
                        "However"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Strange …………………………… it might sound, I don’t enjoy music.",
                    "description": "Strange through it might sound means the same as though it might sound strange. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "however",
                        "though",
                        "but"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}